I Am Vanessa Guillen is a documentary film directed by Christy Wegener.
Vanessa Guillen was 20 years old when she was found murdered at a US Army base.
Rather than submit to silence, her family fought for justice and change.
Self (archive footage), played by Vanessa Guillén.
Self, played by Jackie Speier.
Self, played by Jack Reed.
Self, played by Joni Ernst.
Brenda Song (born March 27, 1988) is an American actress.
Born in Carmichael, California, Song began her career at
the age of six, working as a child model.
She made her screen debut with a guest appearance on the sitcom Thunder Alley (1995), and went on to roles such as the
children's television series Fudge (1995) and the Nickelodeon series 100 Deeds for Eddie McDowd (1999).
She starred in the Disney Channel original film The Ultimate Christmas
Present (2000), which won her a Young Artist Award.
She subsequently signed a contract with Disney Channel and earned widespread recognition for playing the titular character in the action film Wendy Wu:
Homecoming Warrior (2006), and London Tipton in The Suite Life franchise (2005–2011), earning her acclaim and two Young Hollywood Awards.
She additionally played the recurring role of Tia in Phil of the Future (2004–2005), and had starring roles in the television
film Get a Clue (2002), the sports comedy film Like Mike (2002) and the comedy film Stuck in the Suburbs (2004).
Song made her transition into mainstream roles with the critically acclaimed biographical drama film The Social Network (2010) and
went on to roles in the ABC political thriller Scandal (2012–2013), the Fox sitcom New Girl and the sitcom Dads (2013).
In October 2014, she signed a talent holding deal with Fox and 20th Century Fox Television and was subsequently cast in several television pilots
for NBC and CBS, including the medical drama series Pure Genius (2016–2017) and the action drama series Station 19 (2018–2020).
She returned to Disney Channel to provide the voice of Anne Boonchuy in the animated series Amphibia (2019–2022), starred as Madison Maxwell in
the Hulu comedy-drama series Dollface (2019–2022), and provides the voice of Princess Akemi in Blue Eye Samurai (2023–present).
She also appeared in the romantic comedy Angry Angel (2017), the psychological thriller Secret Obsession (2019), the
comedy-drama Changeland (2019), the romantic comedy Love Accidentally and the horror video-game The Quarry (both 2022).
Song earned renewed recognition for starring as a showgirl in the drama film The Last Showgirl
(2024) and a chief of staff in the Netflix series Running Point (2025–present).